Preliminary guide to the Robert Sargent literary papers, 1923-2006 MS2308
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Poetry, 1961-2006; Series 3
  - Poems and other writings, undated; Series 3 Subseries 1
    - Keat's Urn, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - The Layman and Relativity, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Manuscript Correspondence, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Writings (Various Subjects), Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - New Albany, Mississippi, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - An Old Conversation, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Poems Published in Journals, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Poetry Boy, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Poetry Floppy Disks, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Published Poems (Not in books), Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Reviews of Aspects of a Southern Story, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Rorty Class, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Scansions, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Scribblings, Incomplete & Unsatisfactory Poems, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - The Sound of Words, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Stealthy Days, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - They Flee from Me [1 of 2], Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - They Flee from Me [2 of 2], Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - WW Reviews, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Truth is an invented thing, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Ybor City, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Poetry reading supplements, Circa 1980 - 2003; Series 3 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains copies of poems Robert Sargent read at various poetry readings throughout his career as well as correspondence regarding these readings. This subseries also includes slides that were used as part of the poetry presentations. The materials in this subseries range in date from Circa 1980 - 2003.
    - Library of Congress, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Readings 1973-1986, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Readings 1988-2000, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Readings/AA Presentation, Circa 1980's; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Readings/AA Presentation Slides, Circa 1980's; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Robert's Poetry Readings, 2002-2003; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - A Woman From Memphis, 1979-1980; Series 3 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Business records, 1996-2006; Series 3 Subseries 3
    This subseries contains awards and media publicity about Robert Sargent's career as a poet. Records and correspondence regarding the publication of Sargent's books of poetry is also included in this suberies. The materials range in date from 1996-2006.
    - Columbia Merit Award, 1996; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Poetry Business, Circa 2005-2006; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Vance Randolf (Folklonist) Photo, 2006; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Voice of the Hill Article, 2003; Series 3 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Published works, 1961-2003; Series 3 Subseries 4
    This subseries contains copies of poetry journals and other poetry publications in which Robert Sargent's poems were published. The materials range in date from 1961 - 2003.
    - The Aging Connection, American Weave, 1966-1990; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - The Antioch, 1961-1965; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Ariel; b flat, bebop, Scat, 1984-1986; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Bogg - Candelabrum, 1974-1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Cimarron Rreview - Clap hands and Sing, 1976-1991; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - College English - Crotan Review, 1974-1987; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Descant - Ekphrasis, 1980-1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - The Federal Poet - Forum, Undated; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Forum - The Georgia Review, 1967-1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - The Hampden- Review Poetry Review, 1987-2003; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - The Hampden- Review Poetry Review, 1996-2003; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - The Hampden- Review Poetry Review- The Hollins Critic, 1987-2000; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - The Hollow Spring- In The West of Ireland, 1980-1992; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Kansas Quarterly- The Laurel Review, 1987-1992; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - The Louisville Review, 1974-1987; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Mississippi Review- Montpelier Plus 4, 1975-1984; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Negative Capability, 1987-1994; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Negative Capability- New York Quarterly, 1987-1990; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Only Morning in her Shoes- Pembroke Magazine, 1981-1990; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Pembroke Magazine, 1988-1989; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Pembroke Magazine, 1990-1991; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Pembroke Magazine, 1992-1993; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Pembroke Magazine, 1995-1997; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Pembroke Magazine, 1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Pembroke Magazine, 2000-2001; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Pembroke Magazine, 2002-2003; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Phoebus- Poetry, 1987-1996; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Poetry East, 1995-1997; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Poetry East- The Poetry Review, 1966-1994; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Prairie Schooner- Puerto del Sol, 1967-1989; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Radishes and Flowers- Roanoke Review, 1989-1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Sandhills Review, 1991-1993; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Shades of Gray - Shenadoah, 1961-1993; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Songs from Unsung Worlds, 1985; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - The South Carolina Review- South Dakota Review, 1993-1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - The South California Review- Southwest Review, 1974-1980; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Sou'wester, 1979-1981; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - St. Andrews Review, 1987-1990; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Sulpher River, 1992-1998; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Tar River Poetry- Twigs, 1976-1996; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - The University Reviews, 1967-1971; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - The View from the Top of the Mountain - Western Humanities Review, 1965-1981; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Western Humanities Review, 1965-1974; Series 3 Subseries 4 (Box 23, Folder 6)